Finding Aid for Penn Central Transportation Company Records 1835-1981
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- New York Central Railroad Company, 1835-1981; 116 linear feet
  - New York Central Records (following name change from New York Central and Hudson River Railroad Company in December 1914)
    The New York Central Railroad Company series (boxes 60, 71-75) includes annual reports, 1915-1966; minutes of the board of directors, stockholders, and committees for 1914-1950; reports to the Interstate Commerce Commission for most of the period 1920-1960 and for Lessor Companies, 1937 and 1943-1960. Also included are the "Green Books" containing annual reports of the parent company and subsidiaries. Some of the "Green Books" date in the period prior to 1914.
    - Annual meetings and reports
      - Annual Meeting of Shareowners: Reports, 1950-1954; 1956-1967 (Box 71)
      - Annual Reports, 1915-1945; 31 items (Box 71)
      - Annual Reports, 1946-1966; 26 items (Box 72)
    - Annual Reports-Combined Reports
      The subseries consists of published annual reports of the parent company and its subsidiaries, arranged chronologically. These "Green Books," dating from 1904 to 1960, contain brief histories and maps of subsidiary railroads in addition to annual reports.
      - 1904-1907, 4 volumes (Box 254)
      - 1908-1910, 3 volumes (Box 255)
      - 1911-1913, 3 volumes (Box 256)
      - 1914-1916, 3 volumes (Box 257)
      - 1917-1919, 3 volumes (Box 258)
      - 1920-1922, 3 volumes (Box 259)
      - 1923-1925, 3 volumes (Box 260)
      - 1926-1928, 3 volumes (Box 261)
      - 1929-1932, 4 volumes (Box 262)
      - 1933-1936, 4 volumes (Box 263)
      - 1937-1941, 5 volumes (Box 264)
      - 1942-1946, 5 volumes (Box 265)
      - 1947-1951, 5 volumes (Box 266)
      - 1952-1960, 9 volumes (Box 267)
    - Minutes of Board of Directors, Stockholders, and Committees
      - And Index to volumes 1-5, December 28, 1914-February 3, 1922., December 28, 1914-June 14, 1916 (Box 60, Reel 1)
        (Also includes copy of consolidation agreement)
      - June 27, 1916-June 9, 1920 (Box 60, Reel 2)
      - June 14, 1920-May 23, 1923 and Index to volumes 6-10, February 15, 1922-February 23, 1927 (Box 60, Reel 3)
      - May 9, 1923-September 29, 1926 (Box 60, Reel 4)
      - October 7, 1926-May 22, 1929 and Index to volumes 11-15, March 2, 1927-September 3, 1930 (Box 60, Reel 5)
      - June 5, 1929-February 4, 1931 and Index to volumes 16-20, September 1, 1930-February 11, 1936 (Box 60, Reel 6)
      - February 11, 1931-December 5, 1934 (Box 60, Reel 7)
      - December 12, 1934-December 23, 1938 and Index to volumes 21-25, February 28, 1936-April 9, 1941 (Box 60, Reel 8)
      - January 13, 1937-April 9, 1941 (Box 60, Reel 9)
      - And Index to volumes 26-30, April 23, 1941-October 31, 1945, April 23, 1941-March 14, 1945 (Box 60, Reel 11)
      - March 28, 1945-May 14, 1947 and Index to volumes 31-35, November 14, 1945-April 13, 1949 (Box 60, Reel 11)
      - May 28, 1947-October 26, 1949 and Index to volumes 36-38, circa April 1949-May 24, 1950 (Box 60, Reel 12)
      - November 9, 1949-November 8, 1950 (Box 60, Reel 13)
    - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
      - 1920-1928, 3 folders (Box 72)
      - 1929-1933, 1935-1936; 3 folders (Box 73)
      - 1938 (Box 73)
      - 1939, 1 volumes (Box 73)
      - 1940-1943, 2 folders (Box 73)
      - 1945-1947, 3 folders (Box 73)
      - 1948-1960, 9 volumes (Box 74)
    - Reports to the Interstate Commerce Commission: Lessor Companies
      - 1937 (Box 75)
      - 1943-1953, 11 items (Box 75)
      - 1954-1960, 1 volumes (Box 75)
  - New York Central Railroad Company: Subsidiaries
    The records of New York Central subsidiaries (boxes 60, 76-154) are arranged alphabetically by railroad name. The records vary in quantity and quality, but documentation of most of these railroads is meager at best. The amount of material for individual companies ranges from one item to fifteen feet. Often the only records we have for a particular railroad are articles of incorporation or merger and consolidation agreements. Most railroads, however, are represented by one or more of the following types of material: board of directors' minutes, annual reports, reports to the Interstate Commerce Commission, operating statements and other financial records, mortgages, stock registers, and correspondence, usually of the secretary or treasurer. Although minutes are for the most part routine, recording elections of officers and resolutions passed, with little or no commentary, occasionally one finds more valuable information. For example, minutes of the Michigan Air Line Railroad dating from the 1870s contain an interesting discussion of competition with the Michigan Central Railroad.
    The earliest records in this subgroup are minutes of the Buffalo and Mississippi Railroad, which run from 1836 to 1851. Among the railroads that are somewhat better documented than most are the Mahoning Coal Railroad Company, the Lake Erie and Pittsburgh Railway, and the Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Company. The Michigan Central Railroad (boxes 126-140) constitutes the largest group of records among the New York Central subsidiaries, measuring 15 feet and dating back from 1846 to 1960. Records of the Michigan Central Railroad, which was incorporated in 1846, include minutes (1846-1959), correspondence of the secretary and treasurer, financial and legal files, and some early correspondence of the Pension Department concerning employee relations.
    By contrast, the Lake Shore and Michigan Southern Railroad (boxes 118-120), also a subsystem of the New York Central, is sparsely documented, containing only four feet of records, but including a 45-year run of board of directors' minutes (1869-1914). The Lake Shore and Michigan Southern Railroad was incorporated in 1869.
    - Air Line Railway of Michigan
      - Minutes, May 1869 (Box 76)
    - Alliance and Northern Railroad
      - Articles of Incorporation and Minutes, 1891-1902; 1 volumes (Box 76)
    - Amboy, Lansing and Traverse Bay Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1919), 1857 (Box 76)
    - Battle Creek and Bay City Railway Company
      - Articles of Association and Miscellaneous Material, 1888-1890 (Box 76)
    - Battle Creek and Sturgis Railway Company
      - Articles of Association 1884, 1889 (certified 1956) (Box 76)
      - Board Docket, 1921-1960 (Box 76)
      - Certificate of Organization 1884, 1889 (certified 1919) (Box 76)
      - General Ledger, 1890-1935; 1 volumes (Box 76)
      - General Journal
        - 1890-1935, 1 volumes (Box 76)
        - 1936-1955, 1 volumes (Box 76)
      - Minutes, 1889-1969
        - 1889-1944 (Volume 1)
        - 1945-1969 (Box 276)
    - Bay City and Battle Creek Railway Company
      - Minutes, 1889-1916 (Volume 2)
      - Bylaws and Certificate of Organization, 1889-1890 (Box 76)
    - Bay City Belt Line Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1919), 1889 (Box 76)
    - Bay City Street Railway Company
      - Articles of Association and Amendments 1865, 1869, 1874, 1875, 1883 (certified 1919) (Box 76)
      - Mortgage, Satisfaction of, 1931 (Box 76)
    - Beech Creek Railroad Company
      - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 276)
    - Buchanan and St. Joseph Railroad
      - Articles of Association and Minutes, 1894-1912; 1 volumes (Box 76)
    - Buffalo and Erie Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1867-1869; 1 volumes (Box 76)
      - Mortgages, Satisfactions of, 1901; 1910; 1917; 1941 (Box 76)
    - Buffalo and Mississippi Railroad Company
      - Articles of Incorporation and Amendments 1835, 1850 (certified 1908) (Box 76)
      - Minutes, 1835-1851; 1 volumes (Box 76)
    - Buffalo and Mississippi Railroad: Western Division
      - Minutes, 1848-1855; 1 volumes (Box 76)
      - Minutes, January 3, 1853 (Box 76)
        (See Northern Indiana Railroad Company of Laporte County, Minutes, 1851-1853)
    - Buffalo and State Line Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1873), 1849 (Box 77)
      - Minutes, 1849-1869; 2 volumes (Box 77)
    - Canada and Michigan Tunnel Company
      - Minutes, May 4, 1888-August 15, 1905 (Box 60, Reel 52)
    - Canada and St. Louis Railway Company
      - Articles of Agreement and Consolidation, 1887 (Box 77)
    - Canada Southern Bridge Company
      - Journal, General, 1873-1904 (Volume 3)
      - Ledger, General, 1873-1904 (Volume 4)
      - Minutes
        - 1873-1905, 1 volumes (Box 77)
        - August 20, 1873-June 15, 1932 (Box 60, Reel 52)
    - Canada Southern Railway Company
      - Annual Reports to the Railroad Transport Commission, 1969-1970; 1973-1976; 7 items (Box 276)
      - Annual Reports to Shareholders, 1942-1973
        - 1942-1960 (Box 77)
        - 1961-1973 (Box 276)
      - Stockholders annual meetings, 1961-1967 (Box 276)
      - Minutes
        - January 13, 1870-June 6, 1945 (Box 60, Reel 32)
        - June 13, 1945-June 14, 1950 (Box 60, Reel 33)
        - 1920-1960, 14 folders (Box 77)
      - Mortgage, 1883; 1912-1916 (Box 80)
      - Mortgage Bonds: Receipts and Correspondence, 1908-1913 (Box 80)
      - Stock Exchange, Applications to, 1908; 1913 (Box 80)
      - Tax Reports and Statements, 1894-1907 (Box 80)
      - Operating Reports
        - 1945-1947, 3 volumes (Box 80)
        - 1948-1950, 1952; 4 volumes (Box 81)
        - 1953, 1955; 1959; 3 volumes (Box 82)
    - Caro and Lake Huron Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Correspondence 1901, 1903, 1906 (certified 1919) (Box 84)
      - Minutes
        - 1901-1902, 1908; 1 volumes (Box 84)
        - February 5, 1901 (Box 60, Reel 52)
    - Central Trunk Railway Company
      - Minutes
        - 1868, 1871; 1 volumes (Box 84)
        - 1876-1909, 1 volumes (Box 84)
        - June 19, 1868-February 26, 1901 (Box 60, Reel 52)
    - Chatauqua Lake Railroad Company of New York
      - Articles of Association, 1878; 1 volumes (Box 84)
    - Chicago and Canada Southern Railway Company
      - Agreements and Share Transfers, 1871-1872; 1 volumes (Box 84)
      - Articles of Consolidation and Miscellaneous Material, 1871; 1888; 1919-1920 (Box 84)
      - Letterpress Book, 1872-1874 (Box 84)
      - Minutes
        - 1872-1879, 1 volumes (Box 84)
        - 1871-1888 (Volume 5)
        - June 20, 1871-June 7, 1888 (Box 60, Reel 52)
    - Chicago, Indiana and Southern Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports, 1906-1914 (Box 84)
      - Articles of Consolidation and Merger, 1906 (Box 84)
      - Bylaws, 1906 (Box 84)
      - Minutes, 1906-1914; 1 volumes (Box 84)
    - Chicago Junction Railway
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission, 1935; 1937-1950; 1952-1955; 19 items (Box 87)
    - Chicago, Kalamazoo and Saginaw Railway
      - Annual Reports, 1910-1918 (Box 87)
      - Board Dockets
        - 1920-1954 (scattered) (Box 87)
        - 1955-1960 (Box 87)
        - 1961-1966 (Box 276)
      - Lease, 1930 (Box 87)
      - Minutes
        - (volume 1), 1871-September 1916 (Box 87)
        - (volume 2), November 1916-1928 (Box 87)
        - (volume 3), 1929-1981 (Box 276)
        - June 1883-September 1950 (Box 60, Reel 33)
      - Mortgage, 1909; 1913; 1922; 1936 (Box 88)
      - Report to Michigan Commissioner of Railroads, 1902 (Box 88)
    - Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Company
      - Agreements, 1922 (Box 88)
      - Application to Interstate Commerce Commission, 1922 (Box 88)
      - Board Dockets, 1931-1966
        - 1931-1960, 5 folders (Box 88)
        - 1961-1966 (Box 276)
      - Correspondence, 1933-1934; 1945; 1953 (Box 88)
      - Map, 1920 (Box 88)
      - Minutes
        - 1904-October 1911, 1 volumes (Box 88)
        - December 1911-June 1922, 1 volumes (Box 88)
        - September 1922-March 1949, 1 volumes (Box 89)
        - February 1950-May 1958, 1 volumes (Box 89)
        - 1958-1971 (Box 277)
        - 1971-1981 (Box 277)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1908-1920, 16 items (Box 90)
        - 1921-1935, 15 items (Box 91)
        - 1936-1948, 13 items (Box 92)
        - 1949-1960, 12 items (Box 93)
        - 1961-1976, 16 items (Box 277)
    - Cleveland and New Castle Railway Company
      - Board Docket, 1920 (Box 94)
    - Cleveland and Toledo Railroad Company
      - Consolidation Agreement, 1853 (Box 94)
      - Dividend Record, 1868-1869 (Box 94)
        (See: Cleveland, Painesville and Ashtabula Railroad Company, Dividend Record, 1868-1869)
      - Minutes, 1853-1869; 2 volumes (Box 94)
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railway Company
      - Annual Reports, 1897-1898; 1902-1904 (Box 94)
    - Cleveland, Painesville and Ashtabula Railroad Company
      - Dividend Record, 1868-1869 (Volume 23)
      - Incorporation and Name Change, 1848; 1866 (Box 94)
      - Minutes
        - 1849-June 4, 1862, 1 volumes (Box 94)
        - August 1862-June 1868 (Volume 6)
        - 1879-1889 (Box 94)
          (See: Chatauqua Lake Railroad Company, Articles of Association, 1878)
        - June 24, 1879-January 25, 1889 (Box 60, Reel 52)
      - Mortgages, 1898; 1904; 1912; 1918 (Box 94)
    - Cleveland, Painesville and Ashtabula Railroad Company and Cleveland, Columbus and Cincinnati Railroad Company
      - Minutes: Joint Executive Committee, 1852-1855; 1 volumes (Box 94)
    - Cleveland, Port Clinton and Toledo Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1868 (Box 95)
    - Cleveland Short Line Railway
      - Articles of Incorporation and Miscellaneous, 1902-1941 (scattered) (Box 95)
      - Minutes
        - 1902-February 8, 1909, 1 volumes (Box 95)
        - February 8, 1909-1915, 1 volumes (Box 95)
    - Cleveland Union Terminals Company
      - Minute books
        - 1918-1950, 4 volumes (Box 278)
        - 1951-1971 (Box 279)
        - August 26, 1918-November 8, 1950 (Box 60, Reel 19)
      - Minutes of Railroad Committee, 1921-1930; 2 volumes (Box 279)
      - Minutes of Executive Committee, 1927-1938 (Box 279)
      - Stockholders annual reports (Box 280)
      - Board dockets, 1940-1966 (Box 280)
      - Financial miscellaneous (Box 280)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission, 1931-1960; 1969-1976 (Box 281)
      - Program for Ceremony Opening Cleveland Union Station, June 28, 1930 (Box 95)
    - Conewango Valley Railroad Company
      - Act of Incorporation (certified 1914), 1870 (Box 95)
      - Minutes, April-May 1870; 1 volumes (Box 95)
    - Connection Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1870 (Box 95)
    - Danville and Indiana Harbor Railroad Company
      - Articles of Incorporation and Miscellaneous, 1905; 1942 (Box 95)
      - Minutes, February 1905-April 1906; 1 volumes (Box 95)
    - Detroit and Bay City Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Correspondence, 1871; 1873; 1875; 1876; 1881 (Box 95)
      - Minutes
        - 1871-1879, 1 volumes (Box 95)
        - 1881-1917 (Volume 7)
      - Mortgage and Correspondence, 1881; 1913; 1929; 1932-1933 (Box 95)
    - Detroit and Charlevoix Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports, 1910-1915 (Box 95)
      - Articles of Association (certified 1919), 1901 (Box 95)
      - Minutes, 1901-1916; 1 volumes (Box 95)
    - Detroit and Chicago Railroad Company
      - Certificate of Organization, 1888 (Box 96)
      - Minutes, 1888-1914; 1 volumes (Box 96)
    - Detroit and State Line Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1872 (Box 96)
    - Detroit Belt Line Railroad
      - Articles of Association, 1909 (Box 96)
      - Minutes, 1909-1916; 2 volumes (Box 96)
    - Detroit, Delray and Dearborn Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Correspondence, 1913; 1919 (Box 96)
      - Minutes, 1895-1916; 1 volumes (Box 96)
    - Detroit, Hillsdale and Indiana Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1925), 1869 (Box 96)
    - Detroit, Hillsdale and South Western Railroad Company
      - Certificate of Organization and Correspondence, 1875; 1925-1963 (scattered) (Box 96)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1937-1960, 24 items (Box 96)
    - Detroit Manufacturers' Railway Company
      - Board Dockets
        - 1949, 1956-1960 (Box 97)
        - 1961-1967 (Box 282)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors
        - 1902-1927, 1 volumes (Box 97)
        - July 9, 1917-January 30, 1951 (Box 60, Reel 35)
      - Minutes: Stockholders' Annual Meeting, 1956-1960 (Box 97)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1937-1955, 1957-1960; 23 items (Box 97)
        - 1961-1976, 16 items (Box 282)
    - Detroit, Monroe and Toledo Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1855 (Box 98)
      - Minutes, 1855-1914; 1 volumes (Box 98)
      - Mortgage
        - 1856-1857 (Box 98)
        - 1876, 1904; 1915 (Box 98)
    - Detroit River Railroad and Bridge Company
      - Minutes, 1872-1873 (Box 98)
        (See: Canada Southern Bridge Company, Minutes, 1873-1905)
    - Detroit River Railway, Bridge and Tunnel Company
      - Minutes, June-August 1873. (Box 98)
    - Detroit River Tunnel Company
      - Annual reports to Railroad Transport Commission, 1968-1974 (Box 282)
      - Applications to New York Stock Exchange, 1911; 1914 (Box 98)
      - Board Dockets
        - 1918-1922, 1931-1959; 3 folders (Box 98)
        - 1961-1966 (Box 282)
      - Minutes of Board of Directors
        - January 16, 1906-December 12, 1934 (Box 60, Reel 34)
        - May 7, 1936-June 14, 1950 (Box 60, Reel 35)
      - Minutes: Stockholders' Annual Meetings
        - 1934-1960, 4 folders (Box 98)
        - 1961-1967, 7 items (Box 282)
      - Mortgage
        - 1906-1911 (Box 98)
        - 1911-1961 (scattered) (Box 98)
      - Reports to Dominion Bureau of Statistics, Ottawa
        - 1946-1960, 15 items (Box 99)
        - 1961-1962, 2 items (Box 282)
    - Detroit Terminal Railroad Company
      - Minutes, January 20, 1910-May 21, 1951 (Box 60, Reel 35)
      - Operating Statement, 1913 (Box 100)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1937-1945, 9 items (Box 100)
        - 1946-1957, 12 items (Box 101)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 282)
    - Detroit Terminal Railway
      - Articles of Association and Miscellaneous, 1901; 1903; 1919 (Box 102)
    - Detroit, Toledo and Milwaukee Railroad Company
      - Articles of Incorporation and Amendments 1897, 1916 (certified 1908, 1919, 1925, 1956) (Box 102)
      - Board Dockets
        - 1922-1960 (scattered) (Box 102)
        - 1961-1966 (Box 283)
      - Journal, General, 1902-1903 (Volume 8)
      - Ledger, General, 1898-1901 (Volume 9)
      - Minute books
        - 1897-1931, 1 volumes (Box 102)
        - 1932-1969, 1 volumes (Box 283)
      - Minutes of Stockholders' Annual Meetings, 1902; 1905; 1907; 1911; 1916-1967; 7 folders (Box 102)
      - Miscellaneous, 1897; 1902; 1907; 1912; 1938 (Box 102)
    - Detroit Transit Railway
      - Articles of Association and Miscellaneous, 1872; 1903; 1919 (Box 102)
      - Minutes, 1872-1902; 1 volumes (Box 102)
    - Dillonvale and Smithfield Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1901-1927 (Box 102)
    - Dillonvale and Smithfield Railway Company
      - Minutes, 1926-1943 (Box 102)
      - Purchase Agreement, 1927 (Box 102)
    - Dunkirk, Allegheny Valley and Pittsburgh Railroad Company
      - Consolidation Agreements and Correspondence, 1872; 1914; 1920 (Box 103)
      - Ledger, General
        - 1891-1898, 1 volumes (Box 103)
        - 1892-1895 (Volume 10)
      - Minutes, 1873-1914; 1 volumes (Box 103)
      - Mortgage, 1910-1915 (Box 103)
    - Dunkirk, Warren and Pittsburgh Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Correspondence, 1867; 1915 (Box 104)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors, June 8, 1967-May 9, 1970; 1 volumes (Box 104)
    - Dunkirk, Warren and Pittsburgh Railway Company
      - Articles of Consolidation and Correspondence, 1870-1915 (scattered) (Box 104)
      - Minutes
        - Board of Directors, May 14, 1870-December 27, 1872 (Volume 11)
        - Executive Committee
          - May 15, 1871-January 13, 1872, 1 volumes (Box 104)
          - May 15, 1871-November 23, 1872 (Volume 12)
      - Mortgages, 1870; 1872; 1911 (Box 104)
    - Elkhart and Western Railroad Company
      - Minutes
        - May 31, 1888-May 10, 1898, 1 volumes (Box 104)
        - June 12, 1888-February 15, 1915, 1 volumes (Box 104)
      - Mortgage, 1893; 1910; 1913; 1916 (Box 104)
    - Erie and Kalamazoo Railroad Company
      - Mortgage, 1852 (Box 104)
    - Erie and North East Railroad Company
      - Minutes, December 1846-June 1867; 1 volumes (Box 105)
      - Stock Ledger, 1852-1861; 1 volumes (Box 105)
      - Stock Register, 1849-1862; 1 volumes (Box 105)
    - Fairport and Phalanx Railroad Company
      - Articles of Incorporation and Miscellaneous, 1901; 1919 (Box 105)
      - Minutes, 1901-1919; 1 volumes (Box 105)
    - Fort Wayne and Jackson Railroad Company
      - Minute books
        - 1878-1963 (Box 283)
        - 1964-1981 (Box 283)
      - Certificate of Organization and Correspondence 1879 (certified 1887), 1907 (Box 105)
      - President's Files [Kenneth D. Hull, President], 1942-1946; 1954; 2 folders (Box 105)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission (Joint Reports filed under Detroit, Hillsdale and South Western Railroad Company)
        - 1937-1960, 24 items (Box 105)
        - 1962 (Box 283)
    - Fort Wayne, Cincinnati and Louisville Railroad Company
      - Board Docket, 1922 (Box 105)
    - Fort Wayne, Jackson and Saginaw Railroad Company
      - Mortgage, 1871; 1899 (Box 105)
    - Franklin and Clearfield Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1902; 1906 (Box 105)
      - Minutes, 1902; 1909 (Box 105)
    - Franklin Canal Company
      - Minutes, 1849-1854 (Volume 13)
    - Grand River Valley Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Miscellaneous, 1894; 1957 (Box 106)
      - Minutes
        - June 1853-October 1869, 1 volumes (Box 106)
        - January 1870-April 1894, 1 volumes (Box 106)
        - April 1894-October 1918, 1 volumes (Box 106)
      - Mortgages, 1869; 1879; 1886; 1888; 1910; 1917-1918 (Box 106)
    - Grand Trunk Railway of Michigan
      - Articles of Association (certified 1889), 1867-1869 (Box 106)
      - Minutes, 1866-1868; 1 volumes (Box 106)
      - Stock Subscription Books
        - 1865-1866, 1 volumes (Box 106)
        - 1867, 1 volumes (Box 106)
    - Grand Trunk Railway of Northern Indiana
      - Articles of Association, 1868 (Box 106)
      - Stock Subscription Book, 1868; 1 volumes (Box 106)
    - Grayling, Twin Lakes and Northeastern Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1901), 1891 (Box 106)
      - Minutes, 1891-1901; 1 volumes (Box 106)
    - Green Bay and Western Railroad Company (Box 272)
      - Reports to the Interstate Commission, 1962-1968 (Box 272)
    - Hammond and Blue Island Railroad (Illinois)
      - Minutes, 1893-1897 (Volume 14)
    - Hammond and Blue Island Railroad (Indiana)
      - Minutes, 1895-1897 (Volume 15)
    - Hecla Belt Line Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Dissolution 1902, 1914 (certified 1919) (Box 107)
    - Indiana and Lake Michigan Railway Company
      - Articles of Consolidation, 1888 (Box 107)
      - Court Order (re foreclosure), 1899 (Box 107)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission, 1895-1899; 4 folders (Box 107)
    - Indiana and Lake Michigan Railway Company (Indiana)
      - Articles of Association, 1887; 1903-1904 (Box 107)
    - Indiana and Lake Michigan Railway Company of Michigan
      - Articles of Association, 1887 (Box 107)
    - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad Company
      - Abstract of Charges for Delivery of Cars, 1869-1971 (Box 107)
      - Board Dockets
        - 1920-1922 (Box 107)
        - 1931-1960, 15 folders (Box 107)
        - 1961-1967, 2 folders (Box 283)
      - Operating Statements, 1911-1913 (Volume 1)